<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Roxas</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">The Key of Destiny</string>
    <string name="article_text">Roxas, the Key of Destiny (めぐりあう鍵 Meguriau Kagi?, lit. "Serendipitous Key"), is the Nobody of Sora and was Rank XIII within the original Organization XIII, born when Sora took his own heart to restore Kairi\'s. Although Sora\'s heart was soon restored, Roxas continued to endure and exist, oblivious of Sora\'s existence for most of his life. He has the ability to use the Keyblade, and wields light, using it to direct rays that strike opponents with great power. He commands the Samurai Nobodies.
                                \n Roxas was also one of the mysterious hooded figures in Another side, Another story&#8230; and Deep Dive. During the prologue of Kingdom Hearts II, the player controls Roxas until Sora is awakened. In Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days, Roxas is the primary protagonist. This game focuses on the time period between Roxas\'s birth and his departure from the Organization, eventually leading to his capture at the hands of Riku and DiZ.
                                \n Roxas is born when Sora stabs himself with the Keyblade of heart, forged from the hearts of six of the seven Princesses of Heart, in order to free Kairi\'s heart at the cost of his own. However, Sora spends little time as a Heartless, as Kairi\'s light fetches Sora\'s heart from the darkness, restoring him to his former self shortly after he becomes a Heartless. Secret Ansem\'s Report 12
                                \n While Nobodies are normally destroyed along with their Heartless counterparts to restore a complete being, Roxas was able to co-exist with Sora thanks to the unique method that restored him to a complete being. However, as a downside, Roxas lacked any conscious memory of his time as Sora (as the strength of Sora\'s heart allowed him to retain his memories as a Heartless), though Roxas would reflexively respond to things Sora would. At the time of Roxas\'s creation, Sora also held Ventus\'s heart within his own and remained with Sora\'s body and soul when it became a Nobody, resulting in Roxas taking on Ventus\'s features instead of Sora\'s.[1]
                                \n More at: www.khwiki.com/roxas</string>
</resources>
